Viewers all over the world,
wherever you are, whatever medium you are using to view us,
hear Jesus to those in darkness - "Come out, in the name of Jesus!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Every challenge and situation you are in is darkness.
Hear Jesus to those in darkness - "Out, in the name of Jesus!"
To those in captivity - "Be free, in the name of Jesus!"
Freedom!
Whatever situation you are in - freedom from sickness to good health, in the name of Jesus!
To those who are sick - "Be healed!"
To those who are oppressed - "Be delivered!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
With God, all things are possible.
Never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Never a burden Jesus cannot bear.
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear you being free!
You are saved, in the name of Jesus!
You are free, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
Begin to rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!
TT: Mel Flowers 07/07/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 08/07/2018